A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20 FA292
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowship Files, 1920-1993; 2; 242 Box(es)
  - Lade, Hilary - 1980 - England - Chinese Studies, 1979-1990 (Box 117, Folder 952)
  - LaFontaine, Jean Sybil - 1957 - England - Anthropology and Sociology, 1956-1984 (Box 117, Folder 953)
  - Laidler, Keith - 1938 - England - Chemistry, 1938-1988 (Box 117, Folder 954)
  - Laird, Sally - 1979 - England - Soviet Studies, 1978-1982 (Box 117, Folder 955)
  - Lamalfa, Giorgio - 1964 - Italy - Economics, 1961-1980 (Box 117, Folder 956)
  - Lamb, Kenneth - 1953 - England - American Politics, 1952-1988 (Box 118, Folder 957)
  - Lambert, Daniel - 1977 - France - Dance, 1977-1981 (Box 118, Folder 958)
  - Lamble, John - 1933 - England - Naval Architecture, 1933-1976 (Box 118, Folder 959)
  - Lamot, Jean Louis - 1965 - Belgium - Economics, 1965-1987 (Box 118, Folder 960)
  - Lane, John Charles - 1957 - Australia - Aviation Medicine, 1955-1981 (Box 118, Folder 961)
  - Langbein, Frederick - 1955 - New Zealand - Architecture, 1955-1981 (Box 118, Folder 962)
  - Larkin, John - 1965 - Australia - Economics, 1964-1987 (Box 118, Folder 963)
  - Larmen, David George - 1967 - England - Mathematics, 1967-1975 (Box 118, Folder 964)
  - Launois, Robert - 1968 - France - Economics, 1968-1983 (Box 119, Folder 965)
  - Law, Harry Davis - 1958 - England - Biochemistry, 1958-1986 (Box 119, Folder 966)
  - Lawrence, Peter - 1965 - England - Biology, 1965-1986 (Box 119, Folder 967)
  - Le Pelley, Richard - 1934 - England - Entomology, 1934-1979 (Box 119, Folder 968)
  - Lechmere-Oertel, Richard - 1926 - England - Engineering, 1926-1939 (Box 119, Folder 969)
  - Ledderhose, Lothar - 1969 - Germany - Art History, 1967-1977 (Box 119, Folder 970)
  - Ledwidge, William - 1937 - England - History, 1936-1980 (Box 119, Folder 971)
  - Lee, Erastus - 1938 - England - Mechanical Engineering, 1938-1982 (Box 119, Folder 972)
  - Lee, Simon - 1979 - England - Law, 1978-1990 (Box 119, Folder 973)
  - Leech, Geoffrey - 1964 - England - Linguistics and English Language, 1963-1988 (Box 119, Folder 974)
  - Leenhouts, Anna - 1977 - Netherlands - American Literature, 1977-1982 (Box 120, Folder 975)
  - Lees, Francis Noel - 1938 - England - English Literature, 1938-1981 (Box 120, Folder 976)
  - Lefanu, Nicola - 1973 - England - Musical Composition, 1972-1990 (Box 120, Folder 977)
  - Lefevore, Laurence - 1931 - England - Astronomy, 1930-1981 (Box 120, Folder 978)
  - Leggatt, George - 1979 - England - Philosophy of Law, 1978-1986 (Box 120, Folder 979)
  - Lehane, Denis Charles - 1983 - England - International Relations, 1982-1989 (Box 120, Folder 980)
  - Lehane, Denis Charles - 1983 - England - International Relations, 1982-1989 (Box 120, Folder 981)
  - Lehane, Denis Charles - 1983 - England - International Relations, 1982-1989 (Box 121, Folder 982)
  - Lehane, Denis Charles - 1983 - England - International Relations, 1982-1989 (Box 121, Folder 983)
  - Lehane, Denis Charles - 1983 - England - International Relations, 1982-1989 (Box 121, Folder 984)
  - Lehane, Denis Charles - 1983 - England - International Relations, 1982-1989 (Box 121, Folder 985)
  - Lehane, Denis Charles - 1983 - England - International Relations, 1982-1989 (Box 121, Folder 986)
  - Lehane, Denis Charles - 1983 - England - International Relations, 1982-1989 (Box 121, Folder 987)
  - Leibbrandt, Gottfried - 1961 - Netherlands - Political Economy, 1961-1987 (Box 121, Folder 988)
  - Leitch, George - 1953 - England - International Investment, 1953-1983 (Box 122, Folder 989)
  - Lemerle, Paul Georges - 1954 - France - Economics, 1953-1987 (Box 122, Folder 990)
  - Lenearts, Koenraad - 1977 - Belgium - Law, 1977-1982 (Box 122, Folder 991)
  - Lendon, Nigel - 1974 - Australia - Sculpture, 1974-1977 (Box 122, Folder 992)
  - Lenier, Susan - 1981 - England - Creative Writing, 1981-1986 (Box 122, Folder 993)
  - Lennie, Peter - 1972 - England - Electrophysiology, 1972-1982 (Box 122, Folder 994)
  - Lesser, Henry - 1971 - England - American Law, 1970-1985 (Box 123, Folder 995)
  - Lester, Anthony - 1960 - England - Law, 1959-1989 (Box 123, Folder 996)
  - Levy-Lang, Andre - 1963 - France - Business Administration, 1960-1985 (Box 123, Folder 997)
  - Lewis, Gwyneth - 1982 - England - English Literature, 1981-1988 (Box 123, Folder 998)
  - Lewis, Jack Neville - 1952 - England - Agricultural Economics, 1952-1981 (Box 123, Folder 999)
  - Lewis, Peter Watkin - 1968 - England - Painting and Sculpture, 1967-1990 (Box 123, Folder 1000)
  - Lewison, George Richard Grant - 1964 - England - Architecture, 1963-1990 (Box 123, Folder 1001)
  - Leybourne-White, Grace - 1935 - England - Statistics, 1935-1958 (Box 123, Folder 1002)
  - Lickfold, Leslie - 1929 - England - Music, 1929-1956 (Box 124, Folder 1003)
  - Liebreich, Michael David Jonathan - 1988 - England - Business Administration, 1987-1992 (Box 124, Folder 1004)
  - Light, Alfred Charles - 1928 - England - Architecture, 1928-1981 (Box 124, Folder 1005)
  - Lim, Chong-Keat - 1956 - England - Architecture, 1956-1988 (Box 124, Folder 1006)
  - Linklater, Eric - 1928 - England - Literature, 1928-1974 (Box 124, Folder 1007)
  - Lipson, Leslie - 1935 - England - Political Science, 1935-1975 (Box 124, Folder 1008)
  - Lister, Maurice - 1938 - England - Chemistry, 1938-1975 (Box 124, Folder 1009)
  - Littleboy, Reginald - 1925 - England - English Literature, 1925-1981 (Box 124, Folder 1010)
  - Littlechild, Stephen - 1965 - England - Operational Research, 1964-1990 (Box 125, Folder 1011)
  - Littler, Frank - 1935 - England - Architecture, 1935-1959 (Box 125, Folder 1012)
  - Lizzeri, Giancarlo - 1962 - Italy - Economics, 1961-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1013)
  - Lloyd, Matthew - 1984 - England - Film Studies, 1983-1990 (Box 125, Folder 1014)
  - Lodge, David - 1964 - England - American Literature, 1963-1988 (Box 125, Folder 1015)
  - Loeber, Dietrich - 1952 - Germany - International Law, 1952-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1016)
  - Logan, Walter - 1950 - England - Forestry, 1950-1976 (Box 125, Folder 1017)
  - Logan, Walter - 1950 - England - Forestry, 1950-1976 (Box 125, Folder 1018)
  - Lojacono, Gian - 1976 - Italy - Linguistics, 1976-1985 (Box 126, Folder 1019)
  - Lombardi, Vittorio - 1967 - Italy - Economics, 1966-1980 (Box 126, Folder 1020)
  - Long, Anthony Roger - 1977 - England - Public Administration, 1976-1989 (Box 126, Folder 1021)
  - Long, Simon - 1978 - England - Political Science, 1977-1979 (Box 126, Folder 1022)
  - Longuet-Higgins, Michael - 1951 - England - Oceanography, 1950-1990 (Box 126, Folder 1023)
  - Lough, Roger - 1976 - Australia - Rocket Propulsion, 1975-1987 (Box 126, Folder 1024)
  - Lovegrove, Nicholas - 1980 - England - Public Administration, 1979-1986 (Box 126, Folder 1025)
  - Lovejoy, Robin - 1961 - Australia - Theatre, 1961-1986 (Box 127, Folder 1026)
  - Loyd, Francis - 1953 - England - Conservation, 1953-1979 (Box 127, Folder 1027)
  - Luciani, Giacomo - 1970 - Italy - Economics, 1969-1981 (Box 127, Folder 1028)
  - Luff, Peter - 1981 - England - History, 1980-1987 (Box 127, Folder 1029)
  - Luscombe, Roger - 1977 - England - International Relations, 1975-1990 (Box 127, Folder 1030)
  - Lutyens, William David - 1957 - England - Science Education, 1956-1982 (Box 127, Folder 1031)
  - Lynden-Bell, Donald - 1960 - England - Astronomy, 1959-1987 (Box 128, Folder 1032)
  - Lyonette, Kevin - 1962 - England - Latin American Studies, 1962-1967 (Box 128, Folder 1033)
  - Lyttelton, John Westcote - 1955 - England - Chemistry, 1955-1975 (Box 128, Folder 1034)
  - Lyttelton, Nicholas Adrian - 1965 - England - Italian History, 1965-1967 (Box 128, Folder 1035)
  - Macbeath, Alexander Murray - 1948 - England - Mathematics, 1948-1990 (Box 128, Folder 1036)
  - McCaughey, Arnold Patrick - 1969 - Australia - American Art, 1969-1987 (Box 128, Folder 1037)
  - Maccoll, James - 1930 - England - Economics, 1930-1971 (Box 128, Folder 1038)
  - McCombie, Charles William - 1955 - England - Physics, 1954-1975 (Box 128, Folder 1039)
  - McCormick, Barry - 1972 - England - Economics, 1971-1983 (Box 128, Folder 1040)
  - McCrudden, John Christopher - 1974 - England - Law, 1973-1984 (Box 129, Folder 1041)
  - McCutchan, Arthur Inham - 1954 - New Zealand - Water Resource Management, 1954-1985 (Box 129, Folder 1042)
  - McCutcheon, Stuart - 1982 - New Zealand - Animal Science, 1981-1987 (Box 129, Folder 1043)
  - McDaniel, John - 1956 - England - Digital Computers, 1955-1979 (Box 129, Folder 1044)
  - Macdonald, Robert - 1938 - England - Education, 1938-1985 (Box 129, Folder 1045)
  - McDonnell, John - 1964 - England - Law and Politics, 1964-1975 (Box 129, Folder 1046)
  - McDougall, Archibald - 1927 - Australia - International Law, 1927-1955 (Box 129, Folder 1047)
  - McDougall, Ian Ross - 1972 - England - Nuclear Medicine, 1972-1986 (Box 129, Folder 1048)
  - McDowell, Henry - 1935 - South America - Education, 1935-1988 (Box 129, Folder 1049)
  - Macfarlane, William Angus - 1932 - England - Chemistry, 1932-1961 (Box 130, Folder 1050)
  - McGinn, Joseph - 1934 - England - Business Administration, 1935-1938 (Box 130, Folder 1051)
  - McGrath, Noel - 1937 - England - Political Science, 1937-1975 (Box 130, Folder 1052)
  - McGregor, Craig - 1969 - Australia - Literature and Drama, 1969-1987 (Box 130, Folder 1053)
  - Macintyre, Benedict Richard Pierce - 1987 - England - International Relations, 1986-1990 (Box 130, Folder 1054)
  - Macindoe, Stephen - 1939 - Australia - Plant Genetics, 1939-1987 (Box 130, Folder 1055)
  - McIntosh, Angus - 1936 - England - Comparative Literature, 1936-1990 (Box 130, Folder 1056)
  - McIntosh, John - 1981 - Australia - Management, 1980-1986 (Box 130, Folder 1057)
  - McKay, Lindsay - 1973 - New Zealand - Law, 1972-1986 (Box 131, Folder 1058)
  - McKelvie, Allan - 1946 - Scotland - Orthopaedic Surgical Research, 1940-1989 (Box 131, Folder 1059)
  - Mackenzie, Archibald - 1939 - Scotland - Political Science, 1939-1990 (Box 131, Folder 1060)
  - Mackenzie, Ian William - 1977 - England - Business Administration, 1976-1988 (Box 131, Folder 1061)
  - Mackenzie, William - 1954 - England - Philosophy, 1953-1966 (Box 131, Folder 1062)
  - McKerrell, Archibald - 1965 - England - Physics, 1964-1976 (Box 131, Folder 1063)
  - Mackesy, Piers - 1953 - England - History, 1953-1989 (Box 131, Folder 1064)
  - McKilligan, Sheila Ann - 1971 - England - Mathematics, 1970-1987 (Box 132, Folder 1065)
  - McKillop, James - 1978 - England - Nuclear Medicine, 1977-1989 (Box 132, Folder 1066)
  - McKinnon, Kenneth - 1963 - Australia - Education, 1963-1982 (Box 132, Folder 1067)
  - McKinnon, Malcolm - 1982 - New Zealand - International Relations, 1981-1987 (Box 132, Folder 1068)
  - McLachan, Andrew David - 1959 - England - Chemistry, 1958-1984 (Box 132, Folder 1069)
  - McLean, Andrew - 1933 - Scotland - Chemistry, 1933-1982 (Box 132, Folder 1070)
  - MacLean, Hugh - 1935 - England - Semetic Languages, 1935-1960 (Box 132, Folder 1071)
  - MacLellan, George - 1948 - England - Control Engineering, 1948-1984 (Box 133, Folder 1072)
  - Macleod, Norman - 1956 - England - Chemical Engineering, 1955-1987 (Box 133, Folder 1073)
  - McMillan, Hugh - 1934 - Canada - Entomology, 1934-1940 (Box 133, Folder 1074)
  - McMullen, David - 1965 - England - Chinese Studies, 1964-1989 (Box 133, Folder 1075)
  - McNatty, Kenneth - 1977 - New England - Biology, 1976-1980 (Box 133, Folder 1076)
  - McNeill, William - 1932 - England - Forestry, 1931-1982 (Box 133, Folder 1077)
  - McNicoll, George - 1959 - England - Medicine, 1959-1988 (Box 133, Folder 1078)
  - Macqueen, Edith - 1927 - England - History, 1926-1977 (Box 133, Folder 1079)
  - McShane, Robert - 1968 - New Zealand - Architecture, 1968-1980 (Box 133, Folder 1080)
  - Malfroy, Jules Omar - 1928 - England - International Law and Relations, 1928-1958 (Box 133, Folder 1081)
  - Mallaieu, Joseph Percival - 1930 - England - Economics, 1930-1980 (Box 134, Folder 1082)
  - Mallinson, Nora - 1929 - England - History, 1929-1965 (Box 134, Folder 1083)
  - Malvezzi, Giovanni - 1964 - Italy - Banking, 1961-1980 (Box 134, Folder 1084)
  - Mann, Wilfrid - 1936 - England - Physics, 1936-1990 (Box 134, Folder 1085)
  - Manning, Brian - 1957 - England - History, 1956-1959 (Box 134, Folder 1086)
  - Manning, Susan - 1978 - England - Comparative Literature, 1977-1989 (Box 134, Folder 1087)
  - Mansfield, Jonathan - 1962 - England - Architecture, 1961-1984 (Box 134, Folder 1088)
  - Marazzi, Antonio - 1965 - Italy - Anthropology, 1964-1980 (Box 134, Folder 1089)
  - March, Lionel - 1962 - England - Architecture, 1962-1986 (Box 134, Folder 1090)
  - Marchini-Camia, Antonio - 1969 - Italy - European Community and American Law, 1959-1980 (Box 135, Folder 1091)
  - Marchini-Camia, Antonio - 1969 - Italy - European Community and American Law, 1959-1980 (Box 135, Folder 1092)
  - Marconi, Diego - 1974 - Italy - Logic, 1973-1981 (Box 135, Folder 1093)
  - Marenco, Gaetano - 1969 - Italy - Economics, 1969-1975 (Box 135, Folder 1094)
  - Mariti, Paolo - 1968 - Italy - Economics, 1966-1975 (Box 135, Folder 1095)
  - Marjolin, Robert - 1974 - France - Economics, 1974-1976 (Box 135, Folder 1096)
  - Marriott, Roger - 1970 - England - Business Studies, 1969-1978 (Box 135, Folder 1097)
  - Marsh, Roger - 1976 - England - Music, 1976-1990 (Box 136, Folder 1098)
  - Marshall, Charles - 1933 - Australia - Geology, 1933-1975 (Box 136, Folder 1099)
  - Marshall, Charles - 1933 - Australia - Geology, 1933-1975 (Box 136, Folder 1100)
  - Marshall, Robert - 1935 - England - International Relations, 1935-1988 (Box 136, Folder 1101)
  - Marshall, Stephen Rodrick - 1980 - Scotland - Architecture, 1980-1986 (Box 136, Folder 1102)
  - Marshall, Stephen Rodrick - 1980 - Scotland - Architecture, 1980-1986 (Box 136, Folder 1103)
  - Martill, David - 1985 - England - Geology, 1984-1990 (Box 136, Folder 1104)
  - Martin, Gerald Michael - 1971 - England - Area Studies, 1970-1975 (Box 137, Folder 1105)
  - Martin, Paul - 1982 - England - Behavioral Science, 1981-1987 (Box 137, Folder 1106)
  - Martinelli, Alberto - 1966- Italy - Sociology, 1964-1975 (Box 137, Folder 1107)
  - Martino, Antonio - 1966 - Italy - Economics, 1965-1982 (Box 137, Folder 1108)
  - Martinotti, Guido - 1962 - Italy - Sociology, 1961-1975 (Box 137, Folder 1109)
  - Masnata, Francois - 1963 - Switzerland - Political Science, 1962-1975 (Box 137, Folder 1110)
  - Masson, Judith - 1981 - England - Socio-Legal Studies, 1980-1989 (Box 137, Folder 1111)
  - Mathers, Donald - 1949 - England - Philosophy, 1949-1972 (Box 138, Folder 1112)
  - Maudsley, Ronald - 1951 - England - Law, 1950-1981 (Box 138, Folder 1113)
  - Maughan, Deryck Charles - 1977 - England - Business Administration, 1976-1988 (Box 138, Folder 1114)
  - Maupain, Francis - 1966 - France - International Law and Relations, 1965-1980 (Box 138, Folder 1115)
  - Maw, George - 1947 - England - Biochemistry, 1947-1983 (Box 138, Folder 1116)
  - Mayer, Colin - 1978 - England - Economics, 1977-1987 (Box 138, Folder 1117)
  - Mayer, Mark - 1980 - England - Pharmacology, 1980-1984 (Box 138, Folder 1118)
  - Mayne, Edward - 1951 - England - Industrial Studies, 1951-1988 (Box 139, Folder 1119)
  - Mayne, Edward - 1951 - England - Industrial Studies, 1951-1988 (Box 139, Folder 1120)
  - Mayne, Edward - 1951 - England - Industrial Studies, 1951-1988 (Box 139, Folder 1121)
  - Mayne, Edward - 1951 - England - Industrial Studies, 1951-1988 (Box 139, Folder 1122)
  - Mazodier, Pascal - 1968 - France - Economics, 1966-1980 (Box 139, Folder 1123)
  - Mears, Dennison Doyley - 1953 - England - Business Administration, 1952-1987 (Box 139, Folder 1124)
  - Medd, David Leslie - 1958 - England - Educational Building, 1958-1989 (Box 139, Folder 1125)
  - Medd, David Leslie - 1958 - England - Educational Building, 1958-1989 (Box 139, Folder 1126)
  - Meek, John - 1938 - England - Engineering, 1938-1981 (Box 140, Folder 1127)
  - Meerburg, Dirk - 1974 - Netherlands - Law, 1973-1981 (Box 140, Folder 1128)
  - Mees, Alastair - 1973 - England - Control Theory, 1972-1985 (Box 140, Folder 1129)
  - Mefano, Paul - 1966 - France - Music, 1965-1984 (Box 140, Folder 1130)
  - Meijering, Theodore - 1973 - Netherlands - Philosophy of Science, 1972-1987 (Box 140, Folder 1131)
  - Mellor, David - 1950 - England - Chemical Engineering and Philosophy of Science, 1950-1986 (Box 140, Folder 1132)
  - Melville, James - 1934 - England - Biochemistry, 1932-1985 (Box 140, Folder 1133)
  - Merchant, Wilfred - 1937 - England - Engineering, 1937-1965 (Box 141, Folder 1134)
  - Merrill, Frederick - 1936 - England - Electrical Engineering, 1937-1965 (Box 141, Folder 1135)
  - Mestel, Leon - 1954 - England - Astronomy, 1953-1984 (Box 141, Folder 1136)
  - Metcalfe, Margot Emma - 1932 - England - Cytology, 1932-1988 (Box 141, Folder 1137)
  - Metford, John - 1939 - England - Spanish and Latin American Studies, 1939-1984 (Box 141, Folder 1138)
  - Meyers, Jan - 1974 - Belgium - Law, 1971-1982 (Box 141, Folder 1139)
  - Michell, Alistair - 1969 - England - Electrolyte Pathophysiology, 1968-1990 (Box 142, Folder 1140)
  - Michell, Alistair - 1969 - England - Electrolyte Pathophysiology, 1968-1990 (Box 142, Folder 1141)
  - Michelson, Adolf Michael - 1949 - England - Biochemical Genetics, 1949-1975 (Box 142, Folder 1142)
  - Migone, Gian Giacomo - 1964 - Italy - History, 1963-1984 (Box 142, Folder 1143)
  - Milan, Gilbert Mitterand - 1977 - France - Business Administration, 1977-1981 (Box 142, Folder 1144)
  - Miles, Frank Stephen - 1946 - England - Public Administration and International Relations, 1946-1988 (Box 142, Folder 1145)
  - Milgate, Rodney - 1968 - Australia - Painting, 1968-1983 (Box 142, Folder 1146)
  - Milgrom-Friedman, Jeanette - 1982 - Australia - Psychology, 1981-1983 (Box 142, Folder 1147)
  - Millen, Douglas - 1950 - England - Spectrography, 1950-1980 (Box 143, Folder 1148)
  - Miller, Karl Fergus - 1955 - England - American Literature, 1955-1990 (Box 143, Folder 1149)
  - Miller, Nicholas - 1939 - England - Engineering, 1939-1958 (Box 143, Folder 1150)
  - Mills, Herbert - 1950 - England - Modern Languages, 1950-1954 (Box 143, Folder 1151)
  - Mills, Leonard - 1953 - England - Business and Industrial Studies, 1953-1976 (Box 143, Folder 1152)
  - Mills, Stephen Hilary - 1983 - Australia - Political Journalism, 1982-1987 (Box 143, Folder 1153)
  - Mills, Stephen Paul - 1978 - England - Film Studies, 1978-1989 (Box 143, Folder 1154)
  - Milne, Alan - 1952 - England - Philosophy, 1951-1987 (Box 143, Folder 1155)
  - Milner, Ian - 1937 - England - Far Eastern Studies, 1937-1975 (Box 143, Folder 1156)
  - Milow, Keith - 1972 - England - Painting, 1971-1991 (Box 144, Folder 1157)
  - Milsom, Stroud - 1947 - England - History of Law, 1947-1986 (Box 144, Folder 1158)
  - Mims, William Bathurst - 1952 - England - Nuclear Physics, 1951-1986 (Box 144, Folder 1159)
  - Mitchell, Charles Julian - 1959 - England - History, 1959-1984 (Box 144, Folder 1160)
  - Mitchell, Ronald - 1931 - England - Theatre, 1931-1975 (Box 144, Folder 1161)
  - Mitchison, Nicholas - 1952 - England - Zoology, 1952-1964 (Box 144, Folder 1162)
  - Mitterand, Oliver - 1967 - France - Political Science and Business Studies, 1966-1980 (Box 144, Folder 1163)
  - Moe, Ole Henrik - 1954 - Norway - History of Art and Music, 1953-1975 (Box 145, Folder 1164)
  - Molvig, Finn Kaare - 1955 - Norway - Economics and Public Administration, 1954-1975 (Box 145, Folder 1165)
  - Mondadori, Marco - 1972 - Italy - Logic, 1971-1987 (Box 145, Folder 1166)
  - Monger, Karen - 1984 - England - Political Science, 1983-1989 (Box 145, Folder 1167)
  - Monnery, Neil Charles Ashcroft - 1985 - England - Business Administration, 1984-1988 (Box 145, Folder 1168)
  - Monod, Jean Emile Frederic - 1966 - France - Sociology, 1965-1978 (Box 145, Folder 1169)
  - Monsell, Stephen - 1973 - England - Psychology, 1971-1986 (Box 145, Folder 1170)
  - Montgomerie, James Fraser - 1958 - England - International Relations, 1958-1985 (Box 145, Folder 1171)
  - Moodie, Graeme - 1949 - England - Politics, 1949-1975 (Box 145, Folder 1172)
  - Moody, Keith George - 1951 - Australia - Engineering, 1951-1975 (Box 146, Folder 1173)
  - Moore, Ernest - 1934 - England - Hydraulic Engineering, 1934-1975 (Box 146, Folder 1174)
  - Moore, Gerald - 1963 - England - Law, 1962-1986 (Box 146, Folder 1175)
  - Moore, Martin - 1975 - England - Agricultural Engineering, 1974-1988 (Box 146, Folder 1176)
  - Moore, Peter Gerald - 1953 - England - Statistics, 1952-1988 (Box 146, Folder 1177)
  - Moore, Raymond Milton - 1949 - England - Forestry and Natural Resources, 1949-1988 (Box 146, Folder 1178)
  - Moore, Robert Clifton - 1968 - Australia - Broadcast Journalism, 1968-1989 (Box 146, Folder 1179)
  - Moores, Brian - 1964 - England - Operational Research, 1963-1985 (Box 146, Folder 1180)
  - Moreton, Edwina - 1976 - England - Political Science, 1975-1990 (Box 147, Folder 1181)
  - Morgan, Jeremy Paul - 1983 - England - Art History and Painting, 1982-1987 (Box 147, Folder 1182)
  - Morgan, Michael James - 1969 - England - Biochemistry, 1968-1988 (Box 147, Folder 1183)
  - Morgan, Rosemary - 1977 - Australia - Japanese Civilization, 1976-1985 (Box 147, Folder 1184)
  - Morgan, Victor - 1969 - England - Social History, 1968-1986 (Box 147, Folder 1185)
  - Morgans, William Richard - 1928 - England - Physics, 1928-1971 (Box 147, Folder 1186)
  - Moriarty, Michael - 1953 - England - Public Administration, 1953-1980 (Box 147, Folder 1187)
  - Morin, Yves - 1967 - France - Communication Sciences, 1966-1986 (Box 148, Folder 1188)
  - Morley, John - 1967 - England - Business Administration, 1966-1987 (Box 148, Folder 1189)
  - Moroney, Michael - 1975 - England - Music, 1974-1988 (Box 148, Folder 1190)
  - Morris, George - 1968 - England - Business Administration, 1968-1987 (Box 148, Folder 1191)
  - Morris, James Humphrey (Jan) - 1953 - England - International Relations, 1950-1988 (Box 148, Folder 1192)
  - Morris, John - 1950 - England - Psychology, 1949-1980 (Box 148, Folder 1193)
  - Morris, Timothy Richard - 1984 - England - Theoretical Physics, 1984-1988 (Box 148, Folder 1194)
  - Morrison, James - 1956 - England - Physical Chemistry, 1956-1985 (Box 149, Folder 1195)
  - Morrison, Malcolm - 1972 - England - American History, 1971-1987 (Box 149, Folder 1196)
  - Mortier, Denis - 1965 - France - Business Administration, 1965-1987 (Box 149, Folder 1197)
  - Mortimer, Barry Raven - 1957 - England - Government, 1957-1986 (Box 149, Folder 1198)
  - Morton, Rupert James - 1977 - England - Business Administration, 1976-1987 (Box 149, Folder 1199)
  - Morton, Stewart Francis - 1958 - Australia - Architecture, 1958-1975 (Box 149, Folder 1200)
  - Moscati, Roberto - 1968 - Italy - Sociology, 1968-1976 (Box 149, Folder 1201)
  - Moss, Donald - 1976 - Australia - Medicine, 1975-1981 (Box 149, Folder 1202)
  - Mossman, David James - 1954 - England - Diplomacy, 1954-1971 (Box 150, Folder 1203)
  - Mountfield, Peter - 1966 - England - Public Administration, 1966-1988 (Box 150, Folder 1204)
  - Muir, Alan Ramsey - 1955 - England - Histology, 1954-1975 (Box 150, Folder 1205)
  - Muller, Carl Wolfgang - 1964 - Germany - Social Work, 1964-1975 (Box 150, Folder 1206)
  - Mulligan, Hugh - 1933 - England - Pathology, 1932-1982 (Box 150, Folder 1207)
  - Mumby, Ian Garry - 1987 - England - Business Administration, 1986-1989 (Box 150, Folder 1208)
  - Mumford, Edward - 1926 - England - Entomology, 1926-1978 (Box 150, Folder 1209)
  - Mumford, Edward - 1926 - England - Entomology, 1926-1978 (Box 150, Folder 1210)
  - Mundiya, Tariq - 1988 - England - Law, 1987-1989 (Box 150, Folder 1211)
  - Munn, Mary Sibbald - 1955 - Scotland - Business and Industrial Studies, 1954-1990 (Box 150, Folder 1212)